<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Laws on knuxyl.github.io</title>
    <link>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Laws on knuxyl.github.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:13:47 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rule 10</title>
      <link>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:13:47 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-10/</guid>
      <description>I want to add something to address the freedom to travel idea. The requirement for business with insurance companies to travel and registration absolutely should not be ok. i think a rule like, any place owned or maintained by taxed money should be free for public use in its intended way without requirement for registrations, insurance, fees, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule 9</title>
      <link>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:07:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-9/</guid>
      <description>No entity can create laws, rules, or procedures that contradict, constrain, or alter the ideas presented here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule 8</title>
      <link>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:04:21 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-8/</guid>
      <description>Taxation should exclusively and explicitly only be used on income sources.
This coincides with </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule 7</title>
      <link>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:03:54 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-7/</guid>
      <description>Humans have the right to personal privacy without monitoring and/or tracking unless performed by a policing entity that has obtained a warrant based on credible evidence a crime has been committed.
This explicitly includes any form of digital surveillance, digital tracking, or digital monitoring by policing entities. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule 6</title>
      <link>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:02:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-6/</guid>
      <description>Humans have the right to personal property without searches and confiscations unless performed by a policing entity that has obtained a warrant based on credible evidence a crime has been committed including search location(s) and object(s) being searched for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule 5</title>
      <link>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 11:57:13 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-5/</guid>
      <description>Humans have absolute ownership of their personal property without imposition of any requirements, including but not limited to, payments, services, or registrations to maintain ownership of property by any governmental agency.
This explicitly abolishes taxation to maintain ownership, such as property tax. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule 4</title>
      <link>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 11:55:18 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-4/</guid>
      <description>Humans have absolute ownership of their own bodies without imposition on body anatomy, health, or appearance.
This explicitly includes the right to refuse health care and bodily manipulation for any reason. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule 3</title>
      <link>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 11:54:28 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-3/</guid>
      <description>Humans will not endure discrimation due to anything related to their body.
This explicity includes color, shape, automony, gender, and appearance. This explicity includes past, present, or future health conditions or treatments. WIP This needs some work. There needs to be discrimination when hiring someone to move heavy objects when they are not capable of doing such. There needs to be a distinction between businesses and government interaction with people and the interaction of people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule 2</title>
      <link>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 11:51:45 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/rule-2/</guid>
      <description>Humans have the right to ideological expression that does not contradict any ideas presented in any other rule.
This explicitly includes the abolishment of freedom to practice religions that violate this rule, including but not limited to Juadiac religions (Christianity, Islam, Judaism). </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIP New Bill of Rights</title>
      <link>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/laws/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 11:47:03 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://knuxyl.github.io/laws/laws/</guid>
      <description>1 Humans have the right to self-protection and preservation, which explicitly includes unrestricted ownership of any and all weapons and/or tools used by any and all entities used to police them.
This explicitly includes no requirements for tests, registrations, waivers, and insurance. Humans have the right to hold any weapon(s) and/or tool(s) in any place and time as any entity used to police humans is allowed to hold the same weapon(s) and/or tool(s).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
